ozcruising.com.au 2019-03-12

# Privacy Policy | Ozcruising.com.au

Ozcruising Pty Ltd trading as Ozcruising.com.au is a private company registered in Canberra, Australia (ABN 71 123 529 555).

Ozcruising is subject to the National Privacy Principles introduced under Australian privacy. We hereby set out a summary of how we manage your personal information.

### Collection

The core functions of our business (ie. the primary purposes for which we collect personal information) are to facilitate the booking and marketing of our various cruise and travel products. We will not collect personal information unless it is necessary for one or more of these functions or a related activity.

The information will be collected lawfully and fairly, and not in an unreasonably intrusive way. We may collect personal information about you when you deal with us in person or over the phone, send us correspondence (by letter, email or fax) or visit one of our web sites. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that when collecting personal information you are aware of:

  * Who we are and how to contact us;
  * The fact that you are able to gain access to the personal information we have collected about you;
  * The purpose for our collecting the personal information;
  * The organisations to which we would normally disclose that personal information;
  * Any law that requires the personal information to be collected; and
  * What the consequences may be if the personal information is not provided.
  * As far as it is reasonably possible, we will collect your personal information directly from you. If this is not possible and personal information is collected from someone else (eg. a travel agent), we will take reasonable steps to ensure that you are made aware of the matters listed above, unless specific exemptions apply. Sensitive information will only be collected with your consent, unless specific legislative exemptions apply.

### Use and Disclosure

Our general rule is that we will not use or disclose your personal information other than for the purpose stated at the time of collection. If another use is proposed, we will seek your further consent unless that other purpose is related to the original purpose of collection (the “secondary purpose”). For example, you could reasonably expect us to use or disclose your personal information collected from your booking form for the secondary purpose of sending you information about your automatic entitlements to special offers, potential discounts as a past passenger and any special promotions that are on offer.

Whilst we retain various third parties to assist us in our marketing and promotional activities (eg. to administer our “Ozcruising.com.au Newsletter" email service and to maintain an off-site database for information concerning our past passengers), we do not disclose your personal information to anyone else for their promotional use. Similarly, we are not in the practice of purchasing mailing lists (whether post or email) from third parties for our promotional use.

Any promotional information that we send to you (by post or by email) will contain instructions for how you can easily opt out of receiving further notifications. We seek written assurances from parties to whom we may disclose personal information to ensure that they will treat that information in accordance with our privacy policy.

### Data Quality

We will reasonably ensure that the personal information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete and up to date. We encourage you to contact us if you believe personal information we hold about you is incorrect or incomplete in some way. When the information is no longer needed, we will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify that information.

### Data Security

We take reasonable steps to protect the personal information we hold from misuse and loss, and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure in accordance with industry standards. This includes physical security for our office and electronic security (such as password access, encryption and firewalls) for our office network servers and electronic data transfers. All credit card details are transmitted using 128 Bit SSL encryption.

### Access and Correction

Generally, we will give you access to the personal information we have collected about you and we may correct it at your request. If we do not grant your request for access to or for a correction of personal information we have collected about you, we will provide you with a written explanation of the reasons for our decision.

### Further Information about Privacy

If you are in Australia and you would like further information about privacy generally, please contact the Office of the Federal Privacy Commissioner by calling 1300 363 992 or visit the Commissioner’s web site at [www.privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.gov.au/).

To enquire further about our Privacy Policy please email [sales@ozcruising.com.au](mailto:sales@ozcruising.com.au).
